Which Rose Mary School Welcome to all of you guys,
you should carefully look at this test, this is the
chart of Alok Industries,
after placing one above Alok Industries 6, it again
started making a lower circuit and after placing a lower circuit in it,
it again took an upper circuit, went
near it, after going some distance, it again
reached the same place where you can say that it has
a strong support, there is a
support of 25 years here, it has
reached there again, like from that day it
is very bad for you, because of this Alok
Industries has come down so much, if it does
not come from the comment then tell me it would have
definitely reached Akalgarh 35, this is the
search Raj of the industry, before giving the target, we had seen a
lot of printing around it, a
line was proposed in it, in front of which
this target was told to you, still if the festival is over then it will be given, so at the
place where you
can buy and invest in it now because its result is going to be
released in October, which means it will
announce what its result is and
I know that everyone has logged in district
offices of profit because
in this time of corona virus, many backs
and all things are there  All those marks, everything is
made by
Alok Industries, when this is the right time you
can use it here, once the
result of the stairs is today, after that
its share will touch the sky, everyone knows this but send this
message that you have to inform that you have to
invest here and where to invest,
Tubelight can also come down, no one
can tell you a target
because we can see here that the way it went
up till sixty, it is
coming down quite a lot, which has come down to half of it, so whatever you are doing, you have to do it
carefully, so this is all for this video,
if you have not subscribed to your channel, then
subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon
so that you get the
notification of everything first, if you like
this video, thank you